A live performance as in a band or something,
一个现场的演出就像在乐队里或怎样.
so that's like a hundred times better.
真是要好上百倍.
I mean, you just get, you get to feel the music and be part of it.
我意思是说,你可以感受到, 你可以感受到音乐,成为音乐的一部分.
Sometimes it's nice to have more than two or three people.
有时候能有超过两三个人也挺不错的.
Sometimes it's nice when you get a big group of people
有时有一大群人也很好
it can charge you and make you feel like you know why you're there.
可以激发你, 让你感觉你知道自己为什么在那儿.
I think people like the theater just 'cause the feeling of going out and,
我想人们喜欢去剧院是因为, 那种外出的感觉,
you know, preparing for it, sort of, and relax and you go and get something to eat.
you know,为出门做准备, sort of, 放松一下,出去买点东西吃.
Movies are the most common 'cause they're the most around, but I like going to plays.
电影是最常见的,因为到处都是, 但我喜欢看戏.
Yeah, I've been to comedy clubs.
是的, 我去过喜剧俱乐部.
I enjoy them, if I like the show.
如会很开心, 如果我喜欢那场表演的话.
And I enjoy taking in different cultures, going to different plays
我喜欢接受不同的文化, 去看不同的戏.
I also watch a lot of movies and stand-up comedy and, ah, stuff like that, that's pretty much where I go.
我也看许多电影, 看单人喜剧表演, ah,类似那种的, 那就是我常常会去的地方.
You're seeing something that's for real,
你看到的是真实的东西,
versus something that's processed that,
而不是经过加工的东西,
you know, would be the same if you saw it again and again and again;
you know, 仍然是同样的东西, 如果你一遍一遍去看的话,
if you saw the same movie,
如果你看同一部电影,
it's going to be the same next time I see it.
下次再看时, 它还是一样.
I've been to a couple professional theaters and er, I do like the theater, it's very good.
我去过几个专业剧院, er,我确实喜欢戏剧,真的很好.
I do a magic act, and about a 15-minute show and just have fun doing that.
我表演魔术节目, 和一个大约15分钟一场的表演, 愉快地去做.
I try to come out every day, depending on the weather.
我尽量每天都出来,当然也要取决于天气.
I usually change my act, I'd say, each year.
我一般会换节目, 我会说, 每年.
You know, I pretty much, er, spend the winter designing it,
You know, 我常常,er,在冬天设计我的节目,
putting it together and studying what I want to do
排练好, 学习我要表演的东西,
and, you know, some, it takes me, er,about a year to think about what I want to do and how to change it.
and, you know, 我要花大约一年时间来考虑我想做什么, 如何换花样.
So I picked up his guitar and I played the three chords that I knew, D, A, G,
于是我拿起了他的吉他, 弹奏了我知道的三个和弦：D、A、G,
and while I was strumming someone came along
当我漫不经心地弹时  有人从旁边经过,
and threw a pound coin in the case
把一个1英镑的硬币扔在盒子里,
and this light bulb went off in my head and I said, you konw,
于是我灵机一动, 我想,you know,
why am I studying engineering and production when I can maybe do this myself.
为什么我要读工程和生产专业呢 当我也许可以自己做这个事情?